(this["webpackJsonpquiz-app-starter"]=this["webpackJsonpquiz-app-starter"]||[]).push([[0],{10:function(e,t,r){"use strict";r.r(t);var s=r(0),a=r.n(s),n=r(3),i=r.n(n),o=(r(9),r(1));function c(){var e=Object(s.useState)(0),t=Object(o.a)(e,2),r=t[0],n=t[1],i=Object(s.useState)(0),c=Object(o.a)(i,2),l=c[0],w=c[1],u=[{questionText:"What year did we start dating?",answerOptions:[{answerText:"2019",isCorrect:!1},{answerText:"2017",isCorrect:!1},{answerText:"2018",isCorrect:!0},{answerText:"2016",isCorrect:!1}]},{questionText:"What was the first movie we watched alone??",answerOptions:[{answerText:"Avengers: Infinity War",isCorrect:!1},{answerText:"Solo",isCorrect:!0},{answerText:"Deadpool 2",isCorrect:!1},{answerText:"Mama Mia",isCorrect:!1}]},{questionText:"When was the first time we fogged up a car",answerOptions:[{answerText:"Owens party parking lot",isCorrect:!0},{answerText:"Gateway parking lot",isCorrect:!1},{answerText:"Olive and Oil parking lot",isCorrect:!1},{answerText:"Airport parking lot",isCorrect:!1}]},{questionText:"What is our animal childs name?",answerOptions:[{answerText:"Georgie",isCorrect:!0},{answerText:"Hamtaro",isCorrect:!1},{answerText:"Henrietta",isCorrect:!1},{answerText:"Patricia",isCorrect:!1}]},{questionText:"When you showed me your hand with my London gift, where were we?",answerOptions:[{answerText:"KFC",isCorrect:!1},{answerText:"My Diners",isCorrect:!0},{answerText:"Olive and Oil",isCorrect:!1},{answerText:"Adega",isCorrect:!1}]},{questionText:"On that same day, what gift did you buy me?",answerOptions:[{answerText:"A pen",isCorrect:!1},{answerText:"Food",isCorrect:!1},{answerText:"Phone accessories",isCorrect:!0},{answerText:"Tim Tams",isCorrect:!1}]},{questionText:"Which famous star did you intentionally mis-pronounce to me multiple times?",answerOptions:[{answerText:"Guy fierri",isCorrect:!0},{answerText:"Jamie Oliver",isCorrect:!1},{answerText:"Megan Markle",isCorrect:!1},{answerText:"Steve Carrel",isCorrect:!1}]},{questionText:"What was the name of the poem I wrote you?",answerOptions:[{answerText:"Before her",isCorrect:!0},{answerText:"The tree of life",isCorrect:!1},{answerText:"My everything",isCorrect:!1},{answerText:"Love of my life",isCorrect:!1}]},{questionText:"Will you be my valentine?",answerOptions:[{answerText:"Yes",isCorrect:!0},{answerText:"Absolutely",isCorrect:!0},{answerText:"Always",isCorrect:!0},{answerText:"Positively",isCorrect:!0}]},{questionText:"What names did you call me when when took 5 minutes to soul search the other night?",answerOptions:[{answerText:"Bitch",isCorrect:!1},{answerText:"Asshole",isCorrect:!1},{answerText:"Fucking cunt",isCorrect:!1},{answerText:"All of the above",isCorrect:!0}]}];return a.a.createElement(a.a.Fragment,null,a.a.createElement("div",{className:"bg"}),a.a.createElement("div",{className:"app"},r===u.length?l===u.length?a.a.createElement("div",{className:"score-section"},"You scored full points! Your prize is this code: T2K2K-D5SJA-XG2VG-DWU64"):a.a.createElement("div",{className:"score-section"},"You scored ",l," out of ",u.length,", try again!"):a.a.createElement(a.a.Fragment,null,a.a.createElement("div",{className:"question-section"},a.a.createElement("div",{className:"question-count"},a.a.createElement("span",null,"Question ",r+1),"/",u.length),a.a.createElement("div",{className:"question-text"},u[r].questionText)),a.a.createElement("div",{className:"answer-section"},u[r].answerOptions.map((function(e){return a.a.createElement("button",{onClick:function(t){return e.isCorrect&&w(l+1),void n(r+1)}},e.answerText)}))))))}i.a.render(a.a.createElement(a.a.StrictMode,null,a.a.createElement(c,null)),document.getElementById("root"))},4:function(e,t,r){e.exports=r(10)},9:function(e,t,r){}},[[4,1,2]]]);
//# sourceMappingURL=main.64d13990.chunk.js.map